[Never-Ending Summer]
[Episode 3]
Is it pretty?
It really is pretty.
You did a good job on this fish tank.
This is your reward.
Seriously.
Why do you keep looking at me?
I think you are quite different
From what I imagined.
What did you imagine?
I thought you were
The kind of rich boy who was so lazy
That you just basked in the sun every day,
And you didn't need to study,
Or think about the future.
Someone would cook your meals anyway
And spoon-feed you.
Then, you would inherit
The family business when you grew up,
And hire a dozen secretaries,
Pretending to be
A successful young man.
That's exactly what I plan to do.
But you don't look like it.
It's the first time someone said so.
You are a nice man.
You won't hurt others.
You are different from me.
Then, tell me,
Who have you hurt?
How did you know
I was at this pool?
Your secrecy
Was not bad.
But your profile picture betrayed you.
That tree has albinism.
Not many people can see it.
If you can see it,
Take a picture of it,
And use it as your profile picture,
It means you were in a place
Where you could often see it.
I thought no one would
Notice this tree.
I actually quite like it.
It looks very special
And quite different.
People thought it was not pretty enough,
So they moved it
To this corner.
And yet you like it.
But now two people
Have seen it,
Noticed it, and
Both quite like it.
It means the tree is not lonely.
Right?
♪ If you had ever seen the fireflies ♪
♪ Inside my eyes ♪
♪ I think you would understand ♪
♪ Why I embrace the dark ♪
♪ Maybe it's your gravity ♪
♪ That held me back from losing control ♪
♪ When you passed by me by accident ♪
♪ Our paths suddenly overlap ♪
♪ Countless, unforgettable ♪
♪ No time left, so I ♪
♪ Can only fall toward you ♪
♪ Too dazzling, too lonely, it's alright ♪
♪ I believe in this encounter ♪
♪ Landing in the ruins of the galaxy ♪
♪ Exchanging our comets ♪
♪ Suddenly I am certain ♪
♪ This mud all over me ♪
♪ Is the proof of love ♪
♪ I can't remember and can't go back ♪
♪ If you can't hold it tightly, let me ♪
♪ Fly without hesitation ♪
♪ Sorry, I'm too capricious and obsessed ♪
♪ The Milky Way is drowning ♪
♪ If one day you fall into ♪
♪ The gap a light-year away ♪
♪ You'll find ♪
♪ The scattered ashes ♪
♪ Burns my heart ♪
[Big Ocean Motorcycle Workshop]
Friendship.
A friend in need is a friend indeed.
I treasure the friendship in adversity...
Stop reciting it. Come play for a while.
No.
It's no fun playing by myself.
-Let’s play. -No.
I told you I'm going abroad.
Did you think I was joking?
After you go abroad,
We'll have fewer chances to see each other.
Hang out with me for a bit.
Brother.
Let go of me.
That's disgusting.
Are you a motorcycle or something?
Why so fierce?
Don't tell anyone about me going abroad.
I don't want my family and all the people in the school
To know about this.
I see.
You never invite me to the good stuff.
Suit yourself.
I treasure the friendship in adversity.
I treasure
The friendship
In adversity.
Is today the last day?
Yes, the last day.
I want to buy them,
But I don't have enough money.
Yu,
I'll take all these fish.
Where will you keep them?
None of your business.
Find me
A bigger tank.
I'll buy a tank too.
Okay?
Okay, no problem.
You... you bought them all?
I'm rich.
I'll treat you to sashimi some day.
Hurry up, Yu.
Look at that one swimming so far away.
How is it? It's sea.
What are you smiling at?
I'm not smiling.
You did.
I didn't.
I actually quite like
This sea.
Looking at this sea,
What song comes to your mind?
A song?
I thought of one.
Which one?
What about you?
I asked you first.
If you don't tell me, I won't tell you.
Why did you put the betta fish
In the pool too?
Are you stupid?
♪ The narcissus rides a carp, drifting away in sadness ♪
♪ Deep green lurks beneath the sea, stirring the nebula ♪
♪ On countless nights, we move forward ♪
♪ Seeking, waking up and collecting ♪
♪ Crazy love ♪
♪ Say yes, let's start fresh ♪
♪ The first night, my sunset ♪
♪ The whole world, the two of us♪
♪ The city doesn't sleep, ups and downs ♪
♪ Breathing at midnight ♪
♪ Someone lights the fire ♪
♪ The love burns each other ♪
♪ My organs ♪
♪ Every midnight ♪
♪ Being played ♪
Little betta babies,
Let me get you a new home, okay?
Why separate them?
Betta fish will fight if they are kept together.
Didn't you watch
"Animal World" when you were little?
I didn't watch
Much TV as a kid.
My family thought it was too noisy.
It's okay.
Anyway, now you know.
Just don't keep them together in the future.
I just found this.
Change into this.
Don't catch a cold.
You'd change too.
You can change inside.
Why do you want to go abroad secretly?
Because there's no one here I'm attached to.
And then?
Where do you want to go?
As long as I can study what I want,
Anywhere is fine.
If you have a choice,
It's better to be cautious.
You are smart.
What about you? Where are you planning to go?
I don't know.
I haven't thought about it.
I don't have that kind of luxury.
You should be more cautious.
That would be better.
You are good at stuyding.
You're not like me,
Someone
Who has a very laid-back attitude.
Maybe we are the same.
What?
We're both only 18.
We don't have any solutions
Or any choices.
This seems to be
A club's T-shirt.
Are you coming on the day of the parent-teacher meeting?
I heard there's a club festival that day.
People will release balloons together.
They say it'll be quite lively.
No.
I don't have parents.
Besides,
Writing wishes on balloons
Sounds
Boring.
Balloons won't fly up to the sky
And bless us with good grades in the college entrance examination.
They will only get caught in the trees
And then fall down.
What if I say
I want to release balloons with you?
Actually, I have something to ask you too.
It feels like
You're trying to get close to me.
Why?
Which class are you from?
What are you doing?
What are you doing here in the middle of the night?
Come out!
Attention, guys.
Attention!
Yesterday,
An incident occurred in our school
That requires serious criticism
[Teacher's Office]
And a thorough self-reflection.
Two students,
Lu Xixiao from Class 7, Grade 12,
And Zhou Wan from Class 1, Grade 12.
Stole
Lab equipments
And kept goldfish in the swimming pool.
[Work hard and live up to youth and yourself]
This is a serious violation of school rules.
After discussion, we've decided
That they must make a public self-reflection.
Of course,
With such an incident occurring,
We teachers also bear some responsibility,
And also need to self-ref...
-Don’t blame yourself. -As the saying goes...
It's my fault.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Lu Xixiao from Class 7, Grade 12.
This is Lu Xixiao.
Make a serious reflection.
Yesterday,
I not only sneaked into the school
And misused public property,
But also under the guise of doing an experiment,
I incited Zhou Wan from Class 1
To join me.
Now I feel incredibly ashamed.
I feel
I have let down the school,
And my teachers.
And the one I let down the most
Is Zhou Wan.
Zhou Wan is quite something.
I've never seen him
So willingly
Take the blame for anyone.
Isn't that obvious?
Zhou Wan
Would never do such a thing.
It's all your fault for dragging her down.
What's that got to do with me?
It's your fault.
I wasn't even there that day, okay?
I'm Zhou Wan from Class 1, Grade 12.
I'm sorry for letting down my teachers
And my classmates.
I will deeply reflect on myself
And promise it won't happen again.
I hope all students
Will take this as a warning,
Especially
Those boys
Who love showing off.
Behave yourselves.
I'm always watching you.
I'll say it again.
Students of Grade 12,
You don't have much time left.
You can leave.
Go back to class.
[Teacher's Office]
Thank you, sir.
Lu Xixiao.
[Teacher's Office]
Well.
Is this your
First public self-reflection?
We did this together.
You don't have to take
All the blame yourself.
How could this affect me?
I'm leaving sooner or later anyway.
But you are
Graduating soon.
You don't want anything to go wrong
Before the college entrance exam, right?
I don't owe favors.
[Teacher's Office]
I'll treat you after school.
Okay.
[Excellent Writing Exhibition]
♪ I will keep this frozen heart ♪
♪ I think someone will accept it ♪
♪ In my broken heart ♪
[Excellent Writing Exhibition]
[will be repaired.]
♪ It's just that I'm unforgivable ♪
Take it. Let's go
♪ Self-reflection in your heart ♪
Do you want to go back together with me later?
I'll go back later.
♪ Being ignorant doesn't mean ♪
♪ I can do whatever I want ♪
[16 days countdown of college entrance exam]
Give it back.
♪ I seem to have never ♪
♪ Closed the sunroof ♪
Wan.
♪ Let me tell you the stars are shining on the rooftop ♪
Where's Wan, Jiang Yan?
Are you deaf?
Wan.
Why aren't we there yet?
I'm exhausted.
You complained that the bike
Was too slow,
So I took you on a shortcut.
-You’re complaining that you're tired now? -Didn’t I let you
Sit on the back of my bike?
It would have taken only five minutes to get here.
I won't sit on anyone's backseat.
Do you know how many people
[Ms. Zheng's Fast food]
Want to sit on my backseat?
Then, let them sit there.
Uncle Kang.
Wan.
I've set it up. Come on.
I'll make you noodles.
I have a classmate with me today.
Nice motorcycle.
Really?
You know your stuff.
Well, he has a nice motorcycle.
Why didn't you sit on the backseat?
-Why are you pushing this? -I wish everyone could be
Like you.
Can I touch it? Come on.
-Uncle Kang. -Nothing.
[Uncle Kang's Noodle Shop]
Wait, wait a minute.
When I was young,
I loved riding motorcycles.
I rode
Xingfu 250.
It was so cool
To ride it.
I don't think you've ever seen that motorcycle.
My friend runs a dealership.
You should come to visit with me sometime.
Forget it.
I'm too old for that.
Your boyfriend?
Classmate.
You're in love.
-Fen. Fen. -I know Grandma is not here.
Don't try to scare me.
I was just trying to scare you.
Let's go. Come on in.
Hurry.
[Uncle Kang's Noodle Shop]
[Handmade noodles]
What?
Haven't you ever been to a small shop like this?
No.
I want to eat everything on the menu.
What do you usually order?
You don't need to.
I already ordered for you. The special.
The special?
What special?
Something you won't be disappointed with.
For the class I owed you last time,
I'll make it up to you next time.
I have to go to the parent-teacher meeting tomorrow.
Okay.
[Handmade noodles]
How is it?
I had it custom-made.
It will arrive tonight.
It's so big.
So big?
Three delicacies noodles special.
Is it okay?
Eat slowly, don't burn yourself.
Thank you.
This...
Is it good?
My grandma works here.
This is my personal recipe.
You can't get it anywhere else.
Your grandma still works here?
It's a good thing she's not here today.
Here, drinks.
Thank you, Uncle Kang.
No need to thank me. Here.
Wan, I'm going to school tomorrow too
For my granddaughter's parent-teacher meeting.
Want me to give your grandma a ride?
She hasn't been feeling well lately.
The parent-teacher meeting isn't
A particularly grand event.
I won't bother her.
All right.
By the way,
What's the displacement of that bike?
650.
I'll help you pick them.
No worries.
Let me help you.
It's okay.
Do you have any more vegetables?
Why is there so little left?
-Okay. -I'll take some for you.
Grandma, I'm back.
You haven't eaten yet?
Have you eaten?
I did.
You ate noodles as well today?
You had one bowl of noodles
But paid for two.
What are you talking about?
With a boy?
He is just my classmate.
You haven't eaten your noodles yet.
Eat less carbs
But more shrimp.
Oh no.
Jiang Yan was right.
You're hiding something.
So whenever you want to lie,
You will change the subject.
What did Jiang Yan say?
He didn't say anything.
I asked him.
I wouldn't have known if I hadn't asked.
I was shocked.
You've given up on entering Huaqing University.
What's more, you skipped classes,
And got reported and criticised.
Are you trying to make me mad?
It's not that serious.
Not that serious?
I haven't wanted to
Go to school out of town for a long time.
What's so good about other places?
I will feel lonely
If I go to school in another city by myself.
I wouldn't be used to it.
Getting into Huaqing University
Isn't that important to me.
Wan.
You are grown up now,
And you have a lot of ideas.
Your destiny is in
Your own hands.
I won't interfere.
But remember,
All I hope for is
That you can be safe and sound,
Healthy, and happy.
You've even learned how to snitch.
I...
I was just
Afraid that you would get too close to him.
Do you and Lu Xixiao
Have some kind of grudge?
He's quite nice.
And maybe
You two will have a chance...
There won't be such a chance.
He doesn't live
The same kind of life as us.
-Jiang Yan. -I...
I know what I'm doing.
We are friends.
But there are some things
That friends just can't help with.
You can't tell me those things?
I'm sorry.
It's nothing.
I just feel
We've been drifting apart lately.
After all,
You've always been
My only friend.
Do you remember
When we first met?
Yes.
At that time,
I just moved here,
And my mom wasn't in a good state.
You were so scared back then.
You kept hiding here and crying.
After I found you,
We got into a fight.
Because you found this place first.
But later I was willing
To share this place with you.
You are my first friend.
I won't blame you.
And I promise you,
It will be over soon.
Actually,
You can still go to Huaqing University.
Your grandma thinks so too.
It has nothing to do with my grandma.
I haven't figured out yet
What kind of person
I want to become.
What about you?
What kind of person do you want to be?
Someone successful.
And you?
I haven't really thought about it.
At least a kind person.
Why?
Have you not been kind lately?
What do you think?
You hit me again.
I get mad just thinking about it.
If you snitch again,
I won't hang out with you anymore.
I won't.
The moon tonight...
It's so full.
[New message from Lu Xixiao]
Check your Moments.
[Lu Xixiao]
[Moments]
[Lu Xixiao sent a new message]
[Check Moments]
What time is the club festival?
Zhou Wan.
Are you sure you want to do this?
Like a shot arrow,
There's no turning back.
[Check Moments]
15:30.
[Set up notes]
[Loading]
[Information settings]
[Bow and Arrow]
Students,
With the college entrance exam approaching,
I hope you can
[Music Club]
Spare no effort,
Study hard,
And persevere to the very end.
[Hot] [Hot] [Hot]
Well, excuse me, sir.
I know it's today,
But I hit some traffic.
Has Xixiao arrived?
He hasn't stayed at home these past few days.
I've already told him.
That's great.
I was worried that
He would be upset to see me.
I'll be right there.
Okay.
I'll wait for you.
Okay, see you later.
Attention, students.
The balloon release event of
[Lu Xixiao]
The club festival parent-teacher meeting
Will start at 3:30 PM
Punctually.
Parents and students, please
[I'll wait for you at the playground]
Gather at the playground on time
To sign in.
Sorry.
[National Painting Club] [Guitar Club]
Okay. One more.
Three, two, one.
Wan, perfect.
Let me introduce.
-My parents. -I'm sorry.
Come here.
This is my good friend, Wan.
-Hello, uncle and aunt. -Hello.
-Hello. -Hello.
Can you take a picture of me and my parents?
Sure.
Three, two, one.
Okay.
Let me see.
I'll take a picture of you
And your classmate.
Okay, let's take a picture.
Okay, come on.
Good. Closer to the center.
-Do I look good, Dad? -Yes. Take a look.
Very good.
Let me see.
-What do you think? -Nice.
-Good. Good. -Nice.
Okay.
Thank you, uncle.
What are you going to
Write on the balloon later?
If you don't want to be alone,
Come to me.
It doesn't matter what I write.
It won't come true anyway.
That's too realistic.
Attention, guys.
It's 3:00 PM now.
Please hurry up and
Think about your dreams
And your wishes.
-My dream is... -Meng.
I have something to do. I have to go.
Attention!
[Future]
It's 3:20 PM now.
Our activity is about to start.
Please hurry up.
Hurry up.
We will release the balloons
On time later.
I hope my precious daughter
Can be happy every day.
Happy every day.
Success in your studies.
May your dreams come true.
[College Entrance Exam Rally, Let Your Dreams Fly]
Students, be quiet.
Head teachers and class monitors
Of each class,
Please help organize.
Parents, please stay with your kids.
Our balloon-releasing activity
Will start soon.
Students, hurry up and
Write down your wishes and blessings.
Good students also participate in this kind of activity?
Of course.
On the balloons.
Miss Straight-A,
You also participate in this activity?
Is Lu Xixiao here?
No, he said he had something to do.
I haven't written my wish yet.
Okay, time's up.
Count down with me.
Three, two, one.
[College Entrance Exam Rally, Let Your Dreams Fly]
May your dreams come true.
May our dreams come true.
[Mingde Building]
♪ Should I chase freedom all alone ♪
♪ Find an excuse, heed what I've known ♪
♪ Every time I stop and stay ♪
♪ For reasons that fade away ♪
♪ After the long night ♪
♪ I'll find my way, no more lost inside ♪
♪ Thinking about ♪
♪ Fulfilling the last promise ♪
♪ We've both held fragility ♪
♪ Talked through our misery ♪
♪ This time I'm holding tight to your will ♪
♪ Lighting up all the sparks ♪
♪ Hoping it doesn't slip away ♪
♪ In this boring universe ♪
♪ Drifting day by day ♪
♪ Until the day I choose to break away for you ♪
♪ And that's enough to do ♪
♪ Falling into your tenderness ♪
You are late
Because you went to buy balloons?
♪ Slowly being saved ♪
One or two balloons are too boring.
It feels much better
To have so many wishes
All come true at once,
Right?
Come here.
♪ We've both held fragility ♪
♪ Talked through our misery ♪
♪ This time I'm holding tight to your will ♪
♪ Lighting up all the sparks ♪
♪ Hoping it doesn't slip away ♪
♪ In this boring universe ♪
♪ Drifting day by day ♪
♪ Until the day I choose to break away for you ♪
♪ And that's enough to do ♪
Is it a bit too greedy
To make so many wishes?
♪ Falling into your tenderness ♪
If you are not greedy,
What did you
♪ Slowly being saved ♪
Do all this for?
Though I knew that
You have other motives,
I am willing to help you fulfill your wishes.
Just consider it
You owe me one.
Xixiao.
Lu Xixiao.
Thank you.
My wish
Has already come true.
Xixiao.
Here you go. May your dreams come true.
You hasn't made a wish yet.
But letting them go is good too.
You really think you are my mother,
Don't you?
Of course.
Instead of wasting time here,
You should think of a way
To have another son for Lu Zhongyue.
You are my only son.
Zhou Wan.
Mrs. Lu.
Hello. Welcome.
Hello.
What do you think of
Our event this time?
This time it is mainly
To boost the students' morale.
You seem to hate that woman very much.
I hate her.
Does your dad like her very much?
He just needs a woman
Who is pretty, obedient,
And easy to manipulate.
What if she does something
Your dad doesn't like?
That is the original intention of
Our event, right?
Then, he'll dump her.
It is our biggest motivation.
Can't you recognize me,
Mom?